Iván Abad Andréu

Software developer

Profesional Profile

Hi my name is Ivan, and I'm a Software Developer.

I love travel and this provided an experience in programming area in other countries, and I think it's enriching for me because you get to become acquainted with other cultures, languages and people.

Also I do courses about programming on my free time.

Contact Details

C/ Miguel Fleta 17 2B 44600 Alcañiz Spain

(+34) 666 629 533

ivan.abad92@gmail.com

ivanabad.com

Education

CPIFP Bajo Aragon, Alcañiz, Spain Higher Certificate in "WEB development"	2013 - Actuality
Used Java, HTML 5, CSS 3, PHP, Javascript	
IES Santiago Hernandez, Saragosa, Spain Higher Certificate in "Cross-platform development"	2011 - 2013
Used Java, C/C++, VB.net, Android, Oracle, SQL, MySql, XML	
CPIFP Bajo Aragon, Alcañiz, Spain Medium Certificate in "Microcomputer Systems and networks"	2009 - 2011
Used Linux, Windows, W. Server, Office	
LOGOS Formative Centre, Alcañiz, Spain Certificate in "Create and Desing Web pages"	2011 (150 hours)
Used Joomla!, Gimp	
LOGOS Formative Centre, Alcañiz, Spain Certificate in "Videogame programmer"	2010 (250 hours)
Used C/C++, Allegro Library	

Work Experiences

Intern at MoneyMate (Dublin, Ireland)

March 2013 - May 2013

Training period at MoneyMate, QA tester, Full time

Create and Develop unit test in C#, and later created test for Selenium

Intern at INSALUD (Alcañiz, Spain)

June 2011 - July 2011

Training period at INSALUD, SysAdmin section, Full Time

Solved errors who reported de Aragon Health Service workers in their computers

Intern at RS Semily S.R.O. (Semily, Czech Republic)

April 2011 - May 2011

Training period at RS Semily S.R.O. Full Time

Configure computers and solve diferente failures of the clients.

Technical Skills

Vb.Net		HTML 5
Java		CSS 3
C/C++		PHP
Android		Javascript
English Language		Joomla!